It's time for another episode of UpGami, this time with Rin Hashisako of Angerme and Mei Yamazaki of Morning Musume。 24.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I, Hashisako, had my hair changed during the year-end countdown concert.
I had a hair change.
What was the hair change?
I wanted to do something special for the last concert of the year 2023.
I wanted to do something special for the last concert of the year 2023, so I decided to change my hair from rabbit to tatsu.
I wanted to change my hair from rabbit hair to tatsu hair.
In the beginning of the concert, I wore my hair like a rabbit.
But the moment I peeled off my hair, I changed it in a hurry and made it look like the horn of a Tatsu.
That haircut was so sweet and original.
I was approached by other members of the Hello!
We talked a lot and became good friends.
Did you do it yourself?
Yes, I did.
That's amazing!
Teach me next time.
I want you to.
Someday I will.
I, Yamazaki...
I forgot to change the name of my Instagram account from Morning Musume。 23 to '24.
The year 2024 started and we became Morning Musume。 24.
I often forget at this time of the year.
I often say '23' by mistake.
I forgot to change the name of my Instagram account from '23 to '24
How many days since 2024 started?
had said a couple of things.
I hadn't changed it yet.
That's right. I'm writing it right now,
Please check it out. Please do.
This is a very Morning Musume。 I feel like it's a Morning Musume。
That's right. When we take comments,
When we say "2 or 4" for a while, some of them say "2 or 3" by mistake, so please listen carefully.
Please listen carefully.
Now, let's start with the first one, "Up-Kami". Let's start with this time's up-cam, here.
Angerme Life is Beautiful Dance Lesson
Watch the dance lesson of "Life is Beautiful" from Angerme's latest single.
Watch the dance lesson.
Keep moving and the way they move is the same.
It won't change.
And I want to get three nanatas.
All right.
Slant, slant, slant, slant
Chalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
You can turn it big and turn it big and turn it small with 0 life.
I made two turns.
From 1A.
I want to know what that is.
Here we go.
Ready.
Are you greedy? You know what they say. You can look around more freely. Look at the three of them.
Look at them more freely. Take a peek.
Are you greedy? Next.
It's hard today, isn't it?
I'll turn it twice.
I can't take it seriously.
That's right, that's right. That's what I mean.
So tell me how to dance "I'll See You Today.
You don't have to move. Sorry.
I'd like to add a step at the bottom.
And how do you do it?
I don't know.
Ride from the back. Back to front. I want you to ride on the back.
And nod.
That's not right.
Like this. Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. While nodding.
Like looking at a cab.
Yes.
Wait, I want to go diagonally that way.
Yes, go diagonally and stop vertically.
Wait, there's the cab. Wait there cab.
Mmm. Uh-oh.
Oh, I'll take a ride. Nice.
Sounds like fun.
I want to join in.
OK.
This is the practice. This is Mioaka.
It's pretty fulfilling. It's a lot of fun.
So, plus more.
Kawamura-chan and Shimo-chan are together.
Yes, yes, yes. But, but...
I want people to enjoy this dance, not just yell at each other.
That's how it should be.
Hands are free.
You can do your hands freely, but do your legs like this, and do the opposite leg of each other.
Okay.
Ready. Here is a practice. This is Mioaka.
It's pretty fulfilling. It's a lot of fun.
Yes, yes, yes. Try it like this.
And, uh... This. Here's the occasional "jang-jang, jang-jang, jang-jang, jang-jang.
Next, let's see who's going to approach.
You can be in first place now.
Right.
And here are the four in the back.
The one from Tara Tara Tara Tara.
Oh, this one.
Yes, that's it.
Oh, I see. Yes.
Whole body go-go-go.
Here is the practice. This is Mioaka.
Quite substantial. Yay. Yay.
You want to go, don't you? Sha-sha-sha-sha.
They're singing.
I'll be moving around a lot.
I don't know.
More stuff.
Yo. Oh, no.
Tarararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararar. Tararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararararar.
I'll get closer. Looking forward to it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Can I ignore that? There. People who come close to you, right?
OK.
OK, let's do it again with the sound.
Tomorrow, a dead bird... that's what I'm sure of, but I can't decide.
Hopelessness, not disappear, get...
Yes, greed, get started.
Nitrecode. It's not easy.
It's like Beyblade, but with a life of its own.
Kiss it, lay it down, it's not half bad.
Bungy cue, runner, see you at night
I'll do my best, yes, yes, yes, yes
Cab, cab, cab!
This overlight.
I'm going to take a chance on a sub.
I'm going to be very, very good.
I'd like to meet you for once.
Birthday oden, wearing pink
Transformation Gaggan
Shizurechi, sensei.
Yes, it's open.
It's pretty full. It's a lot of fun.
That's right. It's a game.
What a load of crap.
You can worry about that later.
You'll regret it.
You were dancing, weren't you?
KENKENKENKENCHA
Shaningonin in my heart
Life is beautiful
Something like, Yupyong and Hanane, Yuka and Gotohara joined the lower board,
I think this song shows their brightness and sparkle.
Usually, when a new member joins the group, a cool song is usually the first song to be released, like a debut song for the new member,
I am very happy to be able to show that we are a new member with a bright song for the first time in a while.
It's a bright song that fits the image of the two new members, Camillette and I. It's a lot of fun to play,
I think it's a lot of fun to play. I think it's a lot of fun to do.
Lyrics,
I don't want to make 100 dreams come true,
I want to.
As the lyrics say, it's pretty yay.
I'm having fun. I'm enjoying my life.
It really has a sparkling "live is beautiful" feel to it.
It's a very positive feeling.
We did some choreography for the first time today,
There were some changes from the first time, and I felt it got better.
I think we will continue to perform it, so I hope everyone will dance along with us.
Please do.
The lyrics of "Life is Beautiful" are very positive,
When you listen to this song when you are feeling down or depressed today, it will make you feel like it doesn't matter,
I think that if you listen to this song when you are feeling down or depressed today, it will make you feel better and you can enjoy your life,
I hope people who are in that kind of mood to listen to this song,
And the choreography is easy to imitate, so I would like you to dance along,
I would like you to dance along with me.
I could tell from the video that you had a lot of fun during the dance lessons,
I also watched the music video,
I also saw the music video, and everyone was smiling and shining, and I thought the song conveyed the joy of having fun.
That's all for the dance lesson of "Life is Beautiful" by Angerme.
Thank you for everything. I'll be rooting for you, too.
Next up was "Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。 23 Wake Up Call When You Wake Up Vocal Recording
Morning Musume。 23's latest single, Wake Up Call Awakening Moment, please take a look at the vocal recording of Miki Nonaka.
Okay, I'll start with the first A melody and go in order in blocks.
Oh, what's this?
Mm-hmm.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. I prefer my own voice.
Well, everyone's different, but let's try it backwards one time.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
It's a little loose in there.
To you, to you, to you...
Let's get the rhythm going.
And, "not for the sake of it" is firmly put. And I'm going to see him.
I'm coming to see you.
Not for you.
No, it's not.
If I'm going to go with my own voice, I'm going to have to do it better.
Okay, let's do it again.
♪
Okay, let's continue from number one.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I want to say.
"Be cute, be cool, be anguished, be anguished...
A creature with a soul. We have to affirm every face.
Oh, that's good. You're really good.
Maybe you could make the rhythm a little more lively.
And take the accent off the head.
Yes.
Let's make it cute, cool, mawkish, and aimlessly aimless.
I understand.
You're a good actor, too. You have to be positive in every way.
You're so falsetto there.
I have to affirm it.
You have to affirm every face with your own voice, and then switch it up.
Yes, that transition is fun, so let's do that as an added bonus.
Okay, I'm not here for you, unfortunately.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
I'm just trying to be cute, cool, mocking, and mean.
I have to affirm that every creature has a purpose.
OK, sorry. Okay, let's try the B melody.
Creatures with a purpose, we must affirm every kabo.
I'm sure it's boring to leave it up to others. I'll decide for myself, this thought is unshakable.
I don't want to deceive you
Wake up!
I'm sure it's boring to leave it up to others. I can't seem to get into the first three choruses.
Taka-taka-taka-taka-taka-taka-taka-taka-taka-taka!
jaga dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada dada
You should start well.
You're getting too excited.
I want to raise it to the last amount, so the image is to drop it a little. Let's try it again.I want to raise it to the last amount, so I imagine I'll drop it a bit. I think I'll give it one more try.
Now, that was beautiful.
OK, so Chavinko.
The first or second line, I'm getting a little bit long in the end.
Yes.
That's when you wake up the make-up call.
That's when you dress yourself.
I'll make it about as long as I can.
Everyone has caterfluous potential.
It's time to wake up It's time to change your life
Just do it!
Dance baby!
OK!
Yes!
Yes! It was so expensive, but yes!
Thank you!
I can't believe I didn't see it! Should I go faster?
You want me to finish?
Yes!
I'm on a roll.
The Peace can't hear you!
Okay, give him the last one.
Can you give it up?
Yes, I'll give it to you.
Oh, my goodness. You're so excited.
What's going on in there? It's like...
It's embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed to be the one who's asking, "What's going on in there?
That's funny. That's funny.
Back to the head.
Fake-looking thing.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, yeah, about 2345678.
Well, maybe a full eight.
Wow, wow, yay, yay.
Yeah, it's got a little more access.
That's not much of an entrance.That's a weak entrance.
Wow.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
Try to be.
It's fake.
Wow wow yeah
I want to add some nuance.
I got the OK.
Thank you very much.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much
This song has a lot of raps and fakes and formations.
It's a song filled with rap, fakes, formations, etc., but it's also a song with a lot of stuff in it.
But the rhythm is very difficult, and the words are too tight, and it's hard to get the words to come out in time.
But Nonaka-san was really into the rhythm, and I thought it was amazing.
I was really into the rhythm and it was really cool, and more than anything, his falsetto was so beautiful,
I really want to watch this video many times at home to practice my back voice.
That's all for now. 23, Wake up call! This was the vocal recording of Miki Nonaka for Morning Musume。
Thanks for your work!
Rin Hashisako of Angerme and Mei Yamazaki of Morning Musume。 24, Mei Yamazaki is sending this up paper.
Next up is Juice-Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. vocal recording.
From Juice-Juice's latest album, Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Please take a look at the vocal recording of Yume Kudo.
Okay, let's record it then.
First of all, let's start with the A melody, Normal Everyday Life, Normal Happiness.
Normal everyday life, normal happiness
Because I met you, this world is wonderful, isn't it?
If only you were here
This is wanahoo world
Yes, yes, the feeling is already amazingly perfect, so
The end of the ass is a little longer overall
Yes, yes, yes
This world is great if you are here
Yes, that's about the only thing that bothered me
The rest of it looks great. Let's go to the cheese.
Let's go to the cheese. Cheese on the way. Please.
It's a wonderful thing in this world that I found you.
If only you were here.
This is Wanafon World.
Okay, let's go to number two.
Number 2, Emmylou... seven colors of the rainbow.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I guess I'll just do this one then.
Yes, please.
If you can see the seven-color rainbow clearly...
Yes, OK.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's see if we can find the rainbow in the chorus.
I wonder if we've met.
I'm going to start the chorus.
What song are you going to sing?
Okay.
"Since we met, this world is beautiful, isn't it?
"It's a triumphant return to light up the earth.
Okay.
Thank you
You say love me and I say love you
I think I'll just go to the end now.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Please do.
Triumphant return!
You say love me and I say love you
Only you
the two of us
The last part is soooo good. It's like "la la la la run" or "bakorn" but...
You say you love me
This part is hard! It's always difficult!
There's always a cabass in it...
I'm sorry!
I quit the sutra.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry already.
Yes, you can say it with gusto. Yes, you can say it with gusto.
You say you love me and I say I love you
I always sing it softly in my back voice already,
Where is the right place to sing?
If you have a hard time, you can say it with gusto in the last 10 cm.
You say you love me and I say
I'll give it a try. Sorry.
Let's try it.
Excuse me.
There's a little extra here.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's right there.
And then Lara.
I'm sorry.
So, where's the gap?
Excuse me, sir.
Please, sir.
You say love me and I say love you
You say love me and I say love you Only you forever
It's for the both of us
Practice with gusto
You say you love me and I say I love you
I say love me and I say love you
Well, the part about the reel, you can feel it now in your back voice.
I think that's the part where you'll probably get a lot of practice.
Try it with gusto.
No revision.
You say you love me and I say I love you
You say you love me And the rest is totally fine?
Let's just do one line there.
Please.
Revision.
You say you love me
And I say
OK, OK Okay, okay, okay.
Okay. Well, I guess that's all for this day.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I've never experienced re-recording an original song, so it was a strange experience for me.
And even though it was the same song, the members who sang it had completely changed, so I could hear their voices differently, and it was nice to hear different colors.
Yume-chan's hoo after she said "Two" at the end was so cute. Her high notes came out so fast and cool, but her voice was so gentle in the A melody.
I think it's really beautiful.
This is Yume Kudo's vocal recording!
Here it is!
Desiren BA Алれ
Ochamidouma 1st album Channel 1 is now on sale!
It's going to be great!
It's time to say goodbye to the up-dates that Rin Hashisako and Mei Yamazaki have been sharing with you. We've watched a lot of videos this time, and I, Mei Yamazaki, saw the video of Miki Nonaka's vocal recording, and I was so impressed by the way she recorded it.
I hope I can sing as expressively as Ms. Nonaka from now on.
I, Hashisako, was impressed by Yume Kudo's vocal recording.
I was so impressed by Yume Kudo's vocal recording.
I guess it's like this... I tend to worry about pitch and lyrics when I record for the first time, but she sang without worrying about it.
But I felt like it was really great to be able to sing as much as I wanted without worrying about the pitch or the lyrics.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse into the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
This time, up-cam's partners are Rin Hashisako of Angerme and Mei Yamazaki of Morning Musume。 24's Mei Yamazaki. Good bye!
Next time on Upokami,
The next Up-Kami will be a recording session of Red Line by Angerme, and a performance of Tsubaki Factory's "Atarashi",
Tsubaki Factory and Atarizumu's recording.
Please look forward to it!